Guide to the Stephen Sandy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- July 2012 Acquisition, 1945-2012; 16; 3.09; (6 boxes)
  - Writings
    - "Night on the Ontology Ward", circa 2000 (Box 54)
    - "No Dice", circa 2007 (Box 54)
    - "No Natural Enemies", 2005 (Box 54)
    - "North by Northwest", undated (Box 54)
    - "The North End", circa 1960 (Box 54)
    - "Nostrums, Sea Islands", undated (Box 54)
    - "Notes Along Fifth", circa 1980 (Box 54)
    - "Nothing Silver Can", 1980 (Box 54)
    - "O, My Fingers", undated (Box 54)
    - "Of Carrera Domingo", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Old Glory", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Old Lady at Night", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "An Old Observer Near Gloucester", 1960s (Box 54)
    - "On Looking into Latimer's Homer", undated (Box 54)
    - "On the Street", 1990 (Box 54)
    - "Out by the Cemetery", undated (Box 54)
    - "Over Her Thin Body", circa 1990 (Box 54)
    - "Overseas Highway", 1954-1955 (Box 54)
    - "Painters", undated (Box 54)
    - "Pangaea", undated (Box 54)
    - "Passage About India", undated (Box 54)
    - "Pen Doom", undated (Box 54)
    - "Penumbra", undated (Box 54)
    - "Picasso, Drawing", undated (Box 54)
    - "Plaint", undated (Box 54)
    - "Players", undated (Box 54)
    - "Pleiade", undated (Box 54)
    - "Poetry, a Summer NIght", circa 1960 (Box 54)
    - "Point Taken", 2008 (Box 54)
    - "Ponzi", 2008-2009 (Box 54)
    - "Pornographic Novel", 1980s (Box 54)
    - "Possum", undated (Box 54)
    - "Preparation & Independence", circa 2000 (Box 54)
    - "Puss", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Quads", 1980s (Box 54)
    - "Rain are His Words", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Rain Date", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Regime Change", 2007-2008 (Box 54)
    - "Restive", 1985-2009 (Box 54)
    - "Rockhound", 1970-2009 (Box 54)
    - "Rollicking Themes / Victory at Sea", 2000 (Box 54)
    - "The Room", circa 1980 (Box 54)
    - "The Same Water Lapping", 1960s (Box 54)
    - "Sanctum", 1980s (Box 54)
    - "Sang the Turnkey", 2000 (Box 54)
    - "Sap Moon Journal", 1990s (Box 54)
    - "Scholar", circa 1986 (Box 54)
    - "Sea Chest", 2000 (Box 54)
    - "Seamlessly, All the Colors", undated (Box 55)
    - "Sebastian", undated (Box 55)
    - "Second Adulthood", circa 2000 (Box 55)
    - "Segovia", 1960s (Box 55)
    - "Sending", undated (Box 55)
    - "Seniority", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "September 5", undated (Box 55)
    - "Sewing Bird", undated (Box 55)
    - "Shutters", 1986 (Box 55)
    - "Side Hill Farm", 2005-2008 (Box 55)
    - "Silence, Exile, Punning", 2005-2008 (Box 55)
    - "Silver Spoon", circa 1980 (Box 55)
    - "Since Bob the Barber", 2000 (Box 55)
    - "Sketch - New Haven", 2011 (Box 55)
    - "Sky Puddles", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Sleeping End", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Sleigh Ride", 2007 (Box 55)
    - "Smatterer's Companion", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Sojourn, Nara", 1960s (Box 55)
    - "Song, the Old Sponsor", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "South Wall", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Spell", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Spider", 1970s (Box 55)
    - "Spider Lily Going South", 2000 (Box 55)
    - "Splash Down, Aquarius", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Spring Again", 1981-2000 (Box 55)
    - "Starless Summer Night", circa 2000 (Box 55)
    - "Stevens Said to Ted", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Stones", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Straw Men, Red Herring", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Study of Great Man", circa 1960 (Box 55)
    - "Summer Is Us", circa 1987 (Box 55)
    - "Sweet Corn Next", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Swirling in Vapors", undated (Box 55)
    - "Syntactical", 1969 (Box 55)
    - "The Tack", 1992 (Box 55)
    - "Tale of Desire", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "Talk", 1970s (Box 55)
    - "Talk to the Boss", 2000s (Box 55)
    - "Tenants", 1994 (Box 55)
    - "Tender Gothic", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Tense Carries the Whole Texture", 1970s (Box 55)
    - "Terra Nova", 2000s (Box 55)
    - "That Is the Question", 1980 (Box 55)
    - "That Sunday Afternoon", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "The Ways", 1970s (Box 55)
    - "Thirteen", undated (Box 55)
    - "This Was a Staircase", 1957 (Box 55)
    - "Three Songs Without Music", 1980-2012 (Box 55)
    - "Thursday Point", 1980 (Box 55)
    - "To Be a Star", 1990s (Box 55)
    - "To See a Pathogen", 2007 (Box 55)
    - "Tom in the Taconics", 2000s (Box 55)
    - "Tomato Brick Walls", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Tract for People of my Town", 1970s (Box 55)
    - "Trade", 1980s (Box 55)
    - "Triptych", circa 2000 (Box 55)
    - "Twilight in the Coconut Grove", 1980s (Box 56)
    - "Two for Tu Mu", undated (Box 56)
    - "Uncle Boylan", 1960s (Box 56)
    - "Veil", undated (Box 56)
    - "Vellum is No Longer", 1970s (Box 56)
    - "Villanelle Touch & Go", 1960s (Box 56)
    - "Voyage Out", 1960s (Box 56)
    - "Waiting Room", undated (Box 56)
    - "Watching, Dec 1969", 1969-1970 (Box 56)
    - "Watercolors", 1970s (Box 56)
    - "What Fear, But Less Itself", 1990s (Box 56)
    - "What Is this Fugue", undated (Box 56)
    - "White Bull of Marrault", undated (Box 56)
    - "White Space", undated (Box 56)
    - "Winter Aconite", 1990s (Box 56)
    - "With My Back to Life", circa 1970 (Box 56)
    - "When an Overnight Guest", circa 1980 (Box 56)
    - "The World", 1988-1990 (Box 56)
    - "You Could Have It All", 1990s (Box 56)
    - "You Mariners of England", 2008 (Box 56)
    - "You Stagger Out of the Tossing Water", 1960s (Box 56)
    - "Zero Cold Comes Crow Caws", undated (Box 56)
    - "From the Feet of the Master to the Jawbone of an Ass", 1962-1963 (Box 56)
    - "A Low Profile", circa 1990 (Box 56)
    - "Matches", 2001 (Box 56)
    - "A Modern Pastiche", undated (Box 56)
    - "Elder Statesman", undated (Box 56)
    - "The Effect of Dark Matter in Wyoming", 1975-1985 (Box 56)
    - "Questionable Shapes", undated (Box 56)
    - "Epiphany Season", undated (Box 56)
    - "The Mystery of the Day", undated (Box 56)
    - Necessary Mansions, undated; 11 (Box 56)
    - "The Martyrdom of Polycrates", 1984-1994 (Box 56)
    - The Sergeant's Cycle, 1960s (Box 56)
    - "Pat Adams Shows Gemlike Works", 2004 June 26-27 (Box 56)
    - "Singing in Secret", 2004 November-December (Box 56)
    - "John Ashbery", 1990s (Box 56)
    - Bennington Chapbooks in Literature, 1983-1997 (Box 56)
    - Cantata with Henry Brant, 1972-1973 (Box 56)
    - Introduction, Galway Kinnell, undated (Box 56)
    - Interview with Stanley Kunitz, Fall 1998 (Box 56)
    - "Lowell: Memories of B.U. and Harvard", 1975-1985 (Box 56)
    - Introduction, Liam Rector, 2002 (Box 56)
    - "Hercules Oetaeus", 1993-1995 (Box 56)
    - "Trailing Clouds of Glory", 2005 November-December (Box 56)
    - "Seneca in English", circa 2000 (Box 56)
    - "Auden at Bennington", 1997 (Box 56)
    - Robert Frost Stone House talk, 2009 August 9 (Box 56)
    - "Of 'Bronze'", 1988 July (Box 56)
    - "Valéry and Stevens", undated (Box 56)
    - "Manifestations", 1999 (Box 56)
    - "Seeing Things: The Visionary Ardor of Seamus Heaney", 1993 Fall (Box 56)
    - "Gerontion", circa 1998 (Box 56)
    - "Two Days: A Citizen's Trip to Washington", 1970-1971 (Box 56)
    - "Means of Poetry", 1998 (Box 56)
    - Weathers Permitting, 2004-2005 (Box 56)
    - Overlook, 2010, undated; 3 (Box 56)
    - Satori: Poems, 2006 (Box 56)
    - Selected Poems; The Tack, undated (Box 56)
    - Winch, 1980-1982 (Box 56)
    - What It Is, 2007 (Box 56)
  - Other Papers
    - Ned Rorem's musical greeting, 2002 August (Box 56)
    - Library displays, 1989-1999 (Box 56)
    - Sandy Reading, Bennington, 2009 (Box 56)
    - Frost, Birthday Luncheon, 2009 (Box 56)
    - Daron Hagen, 1992 (Box 56)
    - June Arts, 2009, undated (Box 56)
    - Stephen Sandy, first printings, undated (Box 56)
    - Yezzi on "The Thread", 1999 June (Box 56)
    - 2009 Poets' House Showcase (Box 56)
    - "My Minnesota", 1942-1943 (Box 56)
    - Stories from elementary school (and spelling and penmanship tests), 1943-1944 (Box 56)
    - "Five Year Diary", 1944-1947 (Box 56)
    - "Lest We Forget", 1945-1946 (Box 56)
    - "Trips", 1945-1947 (Box 56)
    - Notebook, circa 1946 (Box 56)
    - "Commentaries", 1950-1951 (Box 56)